# Szu-Fang Wang User Experience Designer

szufangwang.com | szufang19@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/szufangwang

#### **Summary**

A UX designer and implementer with over 3-year industrial experience. I am a detail-oriented person with a passion for distilling complicated problems into simple solutions. With interdisciplinary academic backgrounds in design, technology, and business, I focus on designing anesthetic and technical solutions that balance between users and businesses.

#### **Work Experience**

## User Experience Design & Engineer Intern

SelectEd | Providence, RI | April 2019 - Aug 2019

- Doubled the company's income by designing and developing the company's official platform.
- Translated designs and wireframes to build a functional website by using HTML5 and CSS3.
- Utilized Adobe XD for rapid prototyping and optimizing user flow and interface design, increasing follow rate by 56%.

## **Product Designer & Engineer**

MtM+ Technology Corps | Taipei, Taiwan | Jul 2015 - Aug 2018

- Released company's Toolbox mobile application on Google Play, developing it from ideation to launch, designed the entire experience, and coded the application.
- Collaborated with project managers and engineers to transform business requirements and user research results into real-world mobile applications.
- Decreased average operating cost more than 50% by creating visualization dashboards to monitor data in IoT devices for smart factories on Power BI.
- Proactively solved company's inefficient presenting problem by developing a new Android application, increasing company's revenue by 15%.
- Defined and developed company's API as a portal for company's IoT sensors to ensure their high performance.

## Visual Design and Software Engineer Intern

LLD Technology Corps | Taipei, Taiwan | Jan 2015 - Jun 2015

- Designed data structures and data flow to improve data storage and management for a staff card system.
- Defined the architecture, modules, interfaces, and database to operationalize a parking payment system.
- Partnered with engineers to define and deliver new features, test new concepts and assist with final implementation.
- Supported multiple projects simultaneously while meeting tight deadlines.

#### Education

# MS in Human-Computer Interaction

Northeastern University | Boston, MA | Sep 2018 - expected Mar 2020

- Cambodia Center of Human Rights: Starting from analysis research, I managed the team to redesign and to develop a new official website by using Adobe XD and Bootstrap.
- True Ticket: As a design lead, we helped a ticket-selling platform to design a user-friendly mobile application from users' needs and perspectives.

## **BBA** in Computer Science and Information Management

Soochow University | Taipei, Taiwan | Sep 2011 - Jun 2015 Junior/ Senior GPA: 4.0/4.0

• iOrder: Leaded the team to won an excellence award. Including frontend application and backend system, our team brainstormed, prototyped, and developed a multi-function system for customers and restaurants.

#### **Skills**

#### Design

Visual Design
Interaction Design
Sketch
Wireframe
Prototype
Persona
Journey Map
Card Sorting
User Research
Usability Test
A/B Test
Information Architecture

#### Tools

Sketch InVision Balsamiq Adobe XD Adobe Photoshop Adobe Indesign Power BI Eclipse Android Studio GitHub

#### Programming

HTML+CSS JavaScript Java C# MS SQL Python

# Knowledge

Human Interaction
Android Development
Data Analytics
Information retrieval
Artificial Intelligence
AWS Cloud Architecting
E-commerce
Digital Marketing
System Design
Internet of Things

#### **Honors**

**1st Place** Northeastern CPS in Informatics Graduate Project Competition, 2019

#### **Excellence Award**

International ICT Innovative Services, 2014